

Riani Dewi

Software Engineer, UI Design, Customer Relation

+6285155330129

https://dribbble.com/rianidewi18

Jakarta, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

UI Designer

UI Design Freelancing

03/2021 - 08/2021

 Create and design overall concepts for the user experience within a business webpage or product, ensuring all interactions are intuitive and easy for clients.

Customer Support & Head of Operator

CV. Berkah Multisarana

04/2019 - 02/2021

- Handling customers via Whatsapp, Tawk To, Instagram, Telegram and Shopee
- Handle retail transactions (PPOB, Top Up, Token, etc.)
- · Monitoring transaction servers.
- · Monitoring and managing company's website.
- Create, Update, Delete company system app.
- Design menus and banners for the enterprise applications.
- Handle the company's canvasser sales.
- Create and present daily and monthly reports for retail, server and sales.

Secretary Assistant (Work From Home)

National Land Agency (Surabaya)

05/2018 - 03/2020

- · Help researching and revising land documents.
- · Create and present land documents on Microsoft Office.

Online Admin

Yona Batik

09/2018 - 04/2019

- Handling customers on Whatsapp, Instagram, e-Commerce
- Taking product photos to upload on social media.
- Product packaging.
- Help the brands achieve a strong social media presence by handling daily requests.
- · Create and present daily and monthly reports.

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of Competency

05/2018 - Present

Certificate of Internship

11/2016 - Present

SUMMARY

Experienced as an customer support for 2 years. Have expertise in good customer support and can work with clients to meet client needs.

Passionate on IT, design and writing. My goal oriented to pursue a long term career change in the field of Web Design. Have knowledge with analytical skills, problem solving, computer proficient and able to follow up on projects from start to finish.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office : Excel, Word, Power Point, Access

Programming Language: HT

ML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, My Advanced

SQL

Editing Program : Photoshop, Adobe XD, Figma, InDesign

e-Commerce managerial

Advanced

Wordpress, Blogspot Advanced

LANGUAGES

English Fluent
Bahasa Indonesia Native

EDUCATION

Software Engineer SMK Negeri 2, Surabaya 2018

SMP Muhammadiyah 11, Surabaya 2015

SDN Petemon IX, Surabaya 2012